rarelondon.com 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy

We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place.

When you shop on this Website, we will ask you to input and will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password. We may also collect, and our third party providers of advertisements and content may collect, information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms that you entered on our website ("User Information"). We may collect this information even if you do not register with us.

You should be aware that this site is being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service.   
We confirm that any Personal Information which you provide to us (or which is available on public registers) and any User Information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the registration we have with the Data Commissioner's Office. We use your information only for the following purposes:

  * Processing your orders; 
  * For statistical purposes to improve this Website and its services to you; 
  * To serve website content and advertisements to you; 
  * To administer this website; 
  * If you consent, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. 

You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.   
When you create a shopping account while ordering online you will be given the option to receive information from RARE by post, e-mail or telephone, about products, promotions or special offers which we feel may be of interest to you. In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes please e-mail us. (mailorder@rarelondon.com)   
Your Personal Information may be disclosed to other reputable third parties who will help process your order. RARE requires all such third parties to treat your personal information as fully confidential and to fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place.   
You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your Personal Information and /or User Information we are entitled do so.   
Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to us at:

RARE Head Office   
Unit 36  
Wellington Employment Park  
Dunes Way  
Liverpool  
L5 9RJ

Company Registration Number 8345420

VAT Number 159100037
